How did you know?
I'm drinking hot water.
Not even with any flavors, like not even tea bags, just hot water.
Right off the tap.
It's just one of those things I enjoy, you know?
Okay, I am the real nerd.
That's disgusting.
Woo!
Okay.
Thank you, guys.
Are you ready for some Isaac?
Isaac!
Guys, we have a crazy wind streak going right now.
Watch this.
Are you ready?
It's never been this good!
We're gonna keep it at four for now, because I want to do a challenge.
Also, my glasses are dirty.
I realize when I see a bright monitor, you know, that's when the little nasties come out on the glasses.
They become visible.
Gotta take them out.
Okay.
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Cat got your tongue!
Look at this!
We gotta do it!
Dude, that sound just scared me a little bit.
It was so loud.
I need to remove my mouse pad.
There we go.
Okay, so what is this?
Whoa!
We got a lot of HP!
What?
This is easy.
Increases chance of chests as room clear rewards.
Yeah, yeah.
Spawns flies.
Familiar that follows Isaac and can be swung around to deal contact damage?
What?
Blocks enemy shots.
Gains size and damage each time it kills an enemy.
Interesting.
Uh... Oh!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Oh, I see.
I can't shoot.
Oh, this is bad.
So wait, how do I fling this thing around?
Just by walking?
Like this?
That's crazy.
Okay, this is difficult.
I have to... I have to sort of... Ah!
Come on!
Swing at it!
Can I even swing at these?
Oh, I can't... Oh, I can't even do that.
Okay.
I see how it is.
I got flies now.
Uh, so we have this thing.
Notched axe.
No money, though.
There we go.
Oh, crap.
Oh, oh, oh, this is so awkward!
I guess I'll have to rely on the flies.
Also, my mouse pad is still in the way.
Move it out of the way.
Um...
Do I do the boss?
No.
I need to find an item, of course.
Item room first.
Or treasure room.
I guess I could go in there.
I have so much HP, but I don't want to waste a black heart either, right?
Oh, wait!
I can fly!
Oh, okay.
Wait, can I not...
Bro!
Yeah, there we go.
Okay, okay.
Nice.
I guess we can still bomb things.
Oh, wait!
If I can fly, I should probably go in there.
That means I'm only gonna lose half a black heart.
Totally worth!
That was not great.
No money, and I can't buy anything.
Just like real life.
So I can just grab this!
Haha!
Yeah!
Duke of flies...
Flies versus flies!
Oh, shit!
I didn't mean to do that, but I guess that's fine.
Oh, wait!
The poop gets bigger!
Right!
Okay, that's gonna be very nice.
Oh, god.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
I mean, it had to happen, I guess.
Jesus, this is insanely difficult!
There we go, there we go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, there we go.
I think the more speed you have, the better it's gonna be.
You know?
Because you can probably fling the poop further.
That would be my guess.
So, we have one bomb.
I kinda wanna look for a secret.
I think I know where there is one.
Where it always is!
Center of the map.
Oh, wait.
It's not there.
It could be here.
Ah, this is kind of a gamble.
Wait, wait.
No, it's not.
It has to be here.
Yeah!
So good!
I'll explain my reasoning.
Actually, I won't.
I'm gonna keep it a secret.
You'll never know what I'm thinking!
But it was genius, trust me.
It was not luck.
It was skill-based.
Here's.
I'm calling it now, by the way.
This challenge is gonna be easy.
Like, it may look difficult right now.
No.
Satanic Bible!
I told you it was gonna be easy!
Easiest challenge of my life.
Wait a minute.
Uh, yeah, crap this.
Yike!
Let's get the poop in there.
There we go!
Oh wait, does the size reset after each room?
I hope not.
Oh, you can- Wait, you can almost- Oh shit!
Oh!
Okay, that's it.
That's it.
We got it.
I understand how it works now.
Yeah!
Very nice.
Oh god.
Ah, that was bad.
I used my key on that.
Shit.
Whoops.
Oops.
I swing my hammer.
Ba-da-da-dam!
Look at me!
Very nice.
Um...
I am not going to open that.
Just in case I don't get another key.
Haha!
Oh, easy!
I told you it was gonna be easy.
Hello?
More chi- Oh yeah, I can fly, right!
Oh, I really wanna destroy this.
I'm gonna do it.
Never mind, I don't have a bomb.
Kidding.
Uh, wait.
Hmm.
Where's the treasure room?!
Oh!
It's a challenge.
That's why.
Um, openness.
What's that?
Lazy worm?
Hey, I wonder if this actually affects my poop.
I doubt it.
But who knows.
I need a bomb!
Oh, I should've got in here.
Okay.
We're going inside the, um...
The curse room.
Oh, there's also this!
Oh, never mind.
Huh?!
Judas tongue!
Reduces the cost of two hearts...
Devil deal items to- Ooh!
Yo!
Oh!
I like that!
I do indeed!
I'm a fan.
I really wish I could get a bomb.
Or a key.
Either will make me happy.
Little horn.
Oh, yeah?
You like making bombs?
Huh?
I need you to come close- Oh!
Shit!
What the- Okay.
Wait, this guy's kind of annoying on this character?
There we go.
Christ almighty!
Oh god!
There we go!
Good damage!
Very nice.
Uh...
Ooh, wait, wait, wait.
Dry baby.
Blocks enemy shots.
That is very good for me, guys!
That is very good for me!
I'm taking that.
This is an insane item on- on this challenge.
That chromo- It's gonna take us to three out of three?
The problem is it's not gonna do anything for me.
You know, becoming a bookworm means nothing.
Bloody Lust grants a stacking damage bonus.
Uh...
Takes damage.
Maximum six stacks.
Yeah.
I take that.
I'm happy.
Very happy.
Satisfied.
Go.
Definitely doing this run.
Pill!
Yeah!
Health up, baby!
Come here!
I have a feeling this challenge is easier on a controller.
You know, when you have the- The, uh, the stick, you can just sort of spin, right?
Instead of- Having to do this immaculate dance of WASD.
Oh.
Ah!
Dry baby, thank you.
Oh, there we go.
This is so weird.
Yeah!
Okay.
Not bad.
I have to remember that I can fly.
It's actually a big deal.
Let's just get some speed on this.
There we go.
Oh, yeah.
I thought it said the helmet.
Uh, yeah.
Why not?
The hermit.
Uh, I think- no.
Getting a key is not the worst idea.
Booster pack is also an option.
It's on sale.
But I'll come back.
Oh, no.
This is gonna be...
Annoying.
How am I gonna deal with these things?
Oh, God!
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Oh, that was nice!
Well done, me.
I think, uh, the more smaller enemies, the better, because we get to make our poop bigger.
Heh heh.
Money!
Oh!
I needed that.
Um, we're gonna march this one.
Consumes a red heart container to grant a permanent cube of meat.
Uh, no thanks.
I'm good.
I'll take this.
Uh, okay.
So, we got...
Transform all pickups, chests...
Uh, wait.
These are clubs.
So, bombs galore.
That's actually nice.
Wait, we got two of them!
Okay.
Strength.
Hermit.
The last one.
Empress.
Uh, I'm not sure if the damage stat is actually affecting my poop.
I don't know.
The only way I'll know is if I get, uh, spider mod.
I think I'll just keep this for now.
Maybe eat a pill.
Nah.
Let's save the money.
I gotta...
I gotta get some...
Hey, I guess I could turn it into bombs in there.
Ah, but hold on.
I gotta be careful.
Pickups, chests, trinkets, and enemies.
Okay, so enemies.
Roger.
We gotta find a room with a bunch of enemies.
That's when we use this.
That's when we use it.
Okay.
Um, could go in there.
I'm not gonna.
Oh!
That was so bad.
Why are there so many chests and no keys?
Uh, yeah.
Go south.
Oh, how am I gonna deal with this guy?
Oh, okay.
Bomb!
Nice.
Oh, what?
What did I get hit by?
Thank god we have the satanic bible.
You can't reach me.
This is so awkward!
Woo!
Nice.
Come at me!
Ah!
I will swing at you.
Oh my god!
Oh, it's so annoying!
Thank you.
Jesus.
I just got angry.
Hey, I can fly!
Oh my god, look at this.
A room here.
I've never seen anything like this.
This is very unorthodox.
Oh my god.
Terrible performance.
And, uh...
I don't know.
Okay.
Uh, Ace of...
God, man, I...
I gotta use the Ace of Clubs and bring another Ace of Clubs.
Otherwise, it's a waste.
I'm gonna use it in the shop.
Ah, but wait, it's gonna turn all my cards into that, right?
This is a pickup.
Maybe it's fine.
Ace of Clubs.
Fuck it.
Not amazing.
Not, you know, terrible either.
It is what it is.
Alright, then.
We can maybe look for a secret.
Here is an option.
Let's go inside.
Actually, if it is there, then we can...
Oh!
Look at this!
Hey!
Nice!
We got a key as well.
I'm actually gonna save it.
No, I'm not.
Oh!
Nice!
The Fool.
Hmm.
I'm taking a key.
Then we're gonna bomb the shit out of a wall here.
Right there.
Why am I so good at this game?
You can't explain it.
Oh, well, that was...
Annoying.
Didn't even give me anything good.
Yeah.
First time!
I'm happy.
What was that sound?
You heard the...
Sound.
It's back!
Oh, no.
Oh, this thing's gonna be my...
Bane of existence!
Yeah, baby!
Baby!
Yes, baby!
Yes!
Oh, no.
I'm stuck in the left pattern.
I'm not sensing the size of this thing getting bigger, by the way.
That's what she said.
Oh, no!
Yeah!
Yeah, I gotta rely on the baby!
Insanity!
Oh, my God!
Come on, baby!
Very nice, very nice.
More speed is good.
I need speed, I need this.
We're only two red hearts.
It's okay, though.
It's okay.
It's fine.
We're gonna get more.
It is a little questionable, though.
But, yeah.
Let's see how it feels with more speed.
Feels about the same.
Shit.
Up, up, up!
How about I, how about I?
I feel like I'm doing less damage now.
Ooh.
That was a very nice chest.
Sick.
I could go here and use...
I'm gonna do it.
Easy.
Okay, I think the speed definitely does help.
I feel like I'm...
I can throw it farther, you know?
Radius of the orbit is larger.
Arcade...
No.
Oh, God.
Oh, my...
Unpredictable movement enemies are gonna be the worst in this challenge.
Absolutely.
More stuff like this, where he's not even attackable for a lot of the time, you know?
That was nicely done.
Good job, me.
Ooh, that's nice.
Okay, so we have a heart, and...
What is this one?
Voodoo head, additional...
Oh, that's actually pretty good, because I'm flying.
Right?
Um...
Yeah, that's a good one.
The other one is...
Oh, shit, stop shooting me.
Hive mind.
Blue flies and spiders do double damage.
Flying spider familiar is doing...
Man, if only I had the other...
By the way, how am I spawning more flies?
I thought I...
I don't know.
Maybe it's just inherent to this challenge that I just have flies sometimes.
Um...
Well, no, I think I want this.
And then I'll come back for the blue heart.
Do I do that yet?
Yeah, why not?
Gordy!
Look what I got for you!
Oh, that was bad.
Shit.
Whoa, wow.
Hey, not bad!
Whoa, uh...
Wait a sec.
The altar is consumed to sacrifice up to two familiars.
For each familiar sacri...
One random devil room pedestal item is spawned.
Uh...
I think I need my baby.
Like, it is honestly carrying me, you know?
I don't like it.
Maybe I'll change my mind.
Depends, uh...
Whether or not...
Let's say I find, like, a bunch of health pills.
Then I'll do it.
If not, then, uh...
Probably not.
That's the plan.
Oh...
God, that was so bad.
I did not need to lose HP there.
Oh wait, I can actually get it...
Pretty far, look at this.
How am I spawning flies?
Hit him!
Thank you.
Pill, here we go.
Nice!
That is massive.
More coins and bombs.
Ooh, yeah.
Oh!
Didn't get that.
Too bad I can't destroy the poops, huh?
I mean, I could with bombs, but...
Should I really use bombs on that?
I don't think so.
Oh!
Huh?
Wait, what the hell is this?
That feels extremely rare.
Uh, no.
Okay, let's go to...
Fight room.
It's closed, of course.
Okay, I guess we're done.
No!
We're gonna go inside, uh, here.
And we're gonna bomb shit.
Very good.
Success!
I'm sensing a secret room.
This is right smack- Ah, but wait, we can't.
Because it wouldn't be here.
That's like the perfect spot for it.
Centralized.
Let me see the left side.
Okay.
That could be a secret room, actually.
I am amazing!
Come on!
Alright, let's go.
I almost ran into it.
My heart stopped for a brief second.
Oh, man.
Oh no, we're lost.
Okay, so start going south.
Oh.
Wait, those don't damage me?
Wait, the balls don't hurt, or what?
That's new.
Unless I was in this sort of invulnerable state.
Oh shit.
Ah!
Unfair.
Ha-ha!
Amazing.
Uh, yeah.
We're still south.
Uh, oh, you can't go this way, can you?
Oh, that's too bad.
That's too bad.
Oh, I still got hit somehow.
Oh, it was the little fly.
I see now.
Kinda wanna bomb this.
There's so much.
Okay.
That was a waste.
I-I gotta test something real quick here.
Shoot a ball at me.
Okay, the balls do hurt.
Just have to confirm, cause I was like, not 100% sure just now.
I thought they only pushed me, you know?
Oh god.
Wait, this is some bullshit.
Oh, that was a tough room.
Wait, what?
Oh, I see.
Oh no!
Yeah, I mean, how-how is anyone gonna...
do that, you know?
Insanity.
Get me outta here.
Abuse the fact that you can fly!
In every room!
Yeah, this thing ain't getting bigger, by the way.
Unless I'm blind.
I think we reached maximum size.
Oh, this is gonna be a tough one.
I don't even know how I should...
How on earth am I gonna do this?
I-I don't know.
I don't know what to do.
Okay, they're separated now.
Okay.
Hey, this guy killed him for me.
That's nice.
Six coins.
Hey, I could get another heart by taking the battery.
Yeah, maybe.
I'll come back for that.
Wait!
Dude, I just discovered a crazy strategy.
We know where this thing is gonna shoot, right?
I'm gonna position my baby to get hit by it.
Watch.
Oh god.
I forgot about the spiders.
Yeah, how about we kill those guys first, huh?
Oh, okay, they just died somehow.
I don't know what just happened.
How did they die?
Weird.
What the hell is this?
There we go.
Okay, so I'm kinda rich now, so let's go back to the shop.
Peggy bank.
I'm gonna take a lot of damage, right?
Just by the nature of this challenge.
So I think this may actually be worth.
In the long run, guys, it's worth it.
The fallen.
Oh god.
Oh, okay.
He did not die yet.
Thank you, baby.
Ah!
I'm relying on my baby.
Dude, are you fucking kidding me?
Hey, what's this?
Wait a sec.
Oh no.
Is this the end?
Are we dead?
Okay, I don't understand how this baby works.
Each time it blocks a shot, but it did not block a shot just now!
I saw it!
Okay, there it did.
It did there.
I saw it.
A lump of coal.
I mean, that's useless for me, but...
Okay.
Dude, I'm kinda intrigued.
I wanna get this.
Lil' Abaddon.
Abyssal friend.
Following familiar that charges and releases a black ring attack?
Okay.
Now we gotta be really careful with HP, because we are close to death right now.
Very low HP.
Uh...
Also, we still have some money left.
You know what?
Yes.
We gotta get more HP.
Let's get this as well.
The sun!
Uh...
We're gonna save that for next floor, so we can see the map, right?
Oh shit.
Oh, oh my god.
Dude, what is this room?
Why is my little Abaddon not doing shit?
I thought he was gonna charge and do ring things.
Oh!
I gotta charge it myself.
I see.
Heals every floor tile with poop.
Wait, I wonder.
Is the ring gonna affect it?
Oh!
I have a way to strike poops!
That is incredible!
Oh, that's amazing.
This changes things.
A little tough to hit with, but, you know.
Uh...
Yeah.
I mean, that's free for me.
No!
I mean...
That's actually good for me.
Because I wanna keep my current active, right?
I have the perfect active.
No thanks.
No more actives.
Bunch more bombs.
Hey, I can also destroy these now.
Oh, this is gonna be so good.
Also, where are all the...
supposed...
curse rooms gonna spawn?
Because I have the thing that spawns many of them.
But it's not really spawning shit.
I don't know what's going on there.
Anything else we can ring?
I have a feeling, right here.
Ah!
I should've just trusted blindly.
I'm better than this.
Figures the effect of the card...
I mean, that's an active, so we want...
We don't want that.
We do want this.
That's nice.
Whoa!
Holy money!
Wasn't there also a room with a bunch of skulls?
I kinda wanna destroy them.
Somewhere there's a room with a bunch of skulls.
It could be the last floor.
I'm not 100% sure.
I got bombs to spare, okay?
Oh, nice!
Good, good, good.
Oh my god!
How am I so bad?
I should not have lost any HP on that.
That was just catastrophic.
For my future chances here.
Alright, let's leave.
I've had enough of this place.
Actually, let's destroy some skulls.
Okay, but... yeah.
I'm keeping my son.
Go, go, go!
Oh wait, it's...
It's a short one, of course!
Uh-oh!
Wait, how am I gonna deal with...
Guys, we have a problem.
How on earth am I gonna deal with Mom?
I ain't got the capabilities for dealing with that.
I gotta save up HP now.
I cannot mess around.
Good, good, good, good!
Oh, wow!
I'm rich.
Come on, health up!
Health up!
Okay, that works.
Also, I should use the sun.
So I can see all the secrets.
Ooh, very nice.
Uh, let's go straight for the treasure room thingy.
What?!
Wait, they have...
Phantom attacks?!
No way, right?
Holy shit, okay.
Whew!
Uh, yeah, this way.
I don't even know why I went to the right!
Oh my god!
Oh, I'm out of keys!
Guys, we're fucked!
It's actually over.
Come at me!
Okay, that's the strategy.
Okay, good!
Nice!
Very nice.
Uh-oh.
It's fine, it's fine.
Okay, we have bombs, I guess.
We can use that for damage.
Oh, I don't have a key!
I gotta find a key with all these...
Bombs!
And monies!
You can't tell me there's...
No way.
There's no way.
I've pretty much forgotten about my poop.
I'm using the little baby now for damage.
Okay, good.
Another black heart.
Oh.
Oh no.
Hey, look at me!
Wait, can this guy only move left and right?
Huh.
Okay, so we got a...
We got a curse room.
There's also a secret here.
Oh, actually, dude.
That's how we're gonna do this.
We're gonna go in here.
Now we're gonna do this.
That way we can get out of here without taking damage.
Oh, that's huge!
Massive!
That is massive!
Meh!
Very nice!
We really needed that one.
Oh no.
I don't like this.
Okay, I gotta say, my little poop does way more damage than...
Than this circle.
Sick!
Can we hit these guys, please?
There we go.
Actually, how?
Still no key, by the way.
Oh sh...
Go!
Ha!
Oh my god.
Oh!
Yeah!
Bottle steal, baby!
Wow!
Okay.
Okay, spiders.
Oh no.
Can I get out of here without...
Taking damage?
Fine.
Fine!
This room is still closed.
Mmm...
Man, I need keys!
This is such a joke, man.
What is it with the keys?
Wait, wait, we're gonna bomb this.
Wow.
Oh, also...
Nah...
That shop is...
Beckoning me!
This room has a key, trust.
Hey, a battery!
Oh, right.
The fool, yeah.
Oh, actually...
Dude...
I'm gonna look for secrets.
What?
Well, I don't know.
It could be anywhere.
Umm...
Ah, sh...
I mean, there's still a couple of rooms, actually, that we haven't explored.
I almost forgot.
Let's go do that first.
Yeeheehee!
Close one.
Sick.
Kimi, Kimi!
Come on!
Yeah!
The best key of all time, as well!
That is amazing.
Don't hit me, don't hit me.
Okay.
It's all free now.
Oh...
Ah...
Eeeh...
Don't like that.
Hurts my soul.
Wait, is that a...
What is that?
Gigabattery?
Familiar that occasionally spawns a battery pickup?
Grants a...
Ooh...
I mean...
I'm rich.
Why not?!
Yes!
Uh, give me that one.
Alright, this is an underwhelming shop.
The Emperor.
Oh no, what was that one?
Oh, that's the one that takes me to the boss room!
Yeah.
Let me actually bomb this.
What about some secrets here?
Alright, it's probably okay.
I think I...
I think I got what it takes now.
To face the boss.
I'm ready.
Okay.
This should be okay.
I mean, we have like, four black hearts.
That's a lot of damage right there, right?
Oh crap.
Yee-hoo-hoo!
Monkey Paw.
Spawns a black heart.
Isaac returns to...
Ooh...
Nice!
Very nice!
Come on, Mom!
Let's do it, Mom!
I'm just gonna spin to win here.
This is the strategy.
Spin to win!
Dude, I'm killing it!
Thank you for the batteries!
My nose is itchy!
Ah, okay.
It's itchy again!
Timing on that!
I can't focus!
Yeah!
Easy!
I told you it was gonna be easy.
Fucking easy.
Easy!
Nice!
Does that count towards...
Ah, too bad, huh?
Too bad.
Okay.
What's next?
Purist!
Guys, we're doing this.
I'm gonna take a quick bathroom break.
I gotta blow my nose as well.
Okay.
It's time for purist.
Wait, is it actually just...
Wait.
Is this gonna be no items or something?
Like I'm not even allowed to pick up anything?
Because I'm a purist?
I prefer bearskin.
No accessories at all.
Is that it?
Is that the gimmick?
I have a feeling it's gonna be...
Come here.
Oh!
Hey!
What the hell?
Why did that spawn so many bombs?
Okay, well, it looks like there's still items.
Wait, what is this one?
Car battery?
That was the effect, huh?
I'm not gonna get 15 coins on this level.
Uh, yeah.
Why not?
Oh!
This is a good item!
Let's see if I can actually pick it up though.
I have a feeling I'm not gonna be able to.
Never mind!
Guys, this challenge is gonna be easy.
Wait, like, what is this challenge even?
It doesn't even make sense.
What is- where's the challenge here?
Hello?
When is the game getting hard?
Ah, that's funny.
Okay, so we got this, uh...
Okay.
I could blow that up and get the chest, and I think I will.
There's gonna be a bomb in here.
Shit.
Okay, well...
Still decent.
We have one bomb left to- Oh, I know where there's a secret.
It's gotta be on the right here, huh?
Let me see here.
Okay, that's clean.
And I think it's also clean in here.
Yeah.
Soap was used!
Wait, that's, uh...
That's not gonna do anything for me right now.
So I shouldn't pick it up.
Oh yeah!
There's no treasure room.
I was like, wait a minute, where is that?
Damn.
Maybe we'll get some kind of active item from the boss now, and we can use the battery with that, you know?
Widow!
This guy is actually kinda tough.
Just be ready to move at any point.
Now.
Okay, this is getting a little questionable!
Nice!
Okay, that was good.
Range locks.
Ooh, very nice.
That's a buffer for the next floor!
We take that.
Beautiful sniper shots there.
Precision game- What the hell?
Why did you explode?
I still don't understand these enemies, I don't think.
It's a mystery.
Nothing of note happened.
Um, let's not go in there.
After the boss.
Oh!
Nice!
I see something.
I sense it.
I see it.
I feel it.
Oh no.
Very nice.
Dude, this is going amazingly.
How is this a challenge?
Oh!
Money!
I don't have any buffs!
I'm punished for my greed!
Hold on.
We gotta do the boss first.
You know what?
I'm gonna destroy these flames, because I feel like it's gonna bite me in the ass if I don't.
He's somehow harder to hit when he stands still.
I can't explain it.
What's that?
Dude, calm down!
Oh!
Oh no!
Oh.
Okay.
Uh, uh, Moth of the Void.
Grants an additional charge to tag that creates a black ring.
Uh, the ring deals rabid damage to- Ooh!
I like it.
This thing again.
Oh, it's kinda- It's kinda the- Oh, dude.
I should get both and have like the ultimate ring experience.
Guys, you wanna see the ring come out?
We're going ring experience.
The ultimate ring experience.
Watch this.
No!
They charge differently.
Aw, man.
That's gonna be awkward.
I was hoping it was the same charge speed at least.
Oh, well.
That's fine.
Let's go find some bombs.
Oh!
Don't lose HP to these guys, now that we're low HP.
Also, I really should be- Yeah, pre-charging before I go in is what I wanted to say.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Yeah.
Nice.
Ah!
We can uh- okay, okay, very nice.
This one is pretty good.
I may actually get that.
What else did I wanna do?
I wanna- oh, oh!
B-b-b-b-b-bosh, watch this.
We can become ultra mega rich.
Dude, I still thought I could fly.
That's why I went straight.
Uh, here.
Unbelievable.
Oh, 38 monies.
Yoink.
We're also gonna buy a pill because it's gonna be HP up.
Go!
Okay, well.
Uh, this one?
Nice.
Ventricle razor.
Hmm.
I don't care about this.
I don't.
It's, like, extremely underwhelming to me.
Mino carry.
Yeah.
Okay, pre-charge.
And go.
Good.
Oh, we even have a thingy here.
Oh, I don't have HP for this!
Unless we're smart.
Hold on.
Oh, there's enemies.
But they're not charged because I don't have an active.
Dude, we got a smelter.
Um, I can give this guy coins.
Two pills.
Wants a random pill.
Guys, we could take this!
Get a health up pill!
Heh.
And move on.
Can't re-roll, unfortunately.
Mmm, I'm gonna donate.
Oh, no!
It's the battery man!
We don't like that.
I... I'm actually tempted to do this one, guys.
Watch it be health up.
No!
It's a bad damage!
Guys!
Shit.
Guys, I may have messed this up!
This is a mistake!
I have done goofed.
Da-da-da-dum, da-dum, da-dum, da-dum.
At least we get a half a heart there.
Oh, no.
We need more bombs.
I'm- I'm- I'm gonna- Oh, no!
I may have done a little oopsio- No!
Wait, did we kill the boss there?
I don't remember!
I don't know if we did!
Shit!
Guys, I f- How the fuck this went up so bad in the span of like...
Three minutes.
This is bad.
I actually can't believe it.
Oi-oi-oi.
We cannot be losing HP anymore.
This is forbidden.
Oh, my butt!
I'm stuck!
Wait!
I thought all pills are good?!
Guys, I miss- I misunderstood it.
I thought it- I thought it said all pills are good.
That's why I was like, We're gonna get HP up!
Well...
If it- if I had known it didn't say that, I wouldn't have done this.
Just letting you know now.
I'm gonna let you know, right now, that I- You know, speaking.
It's a thing.
Hey, at least we got rings.
Ring gameplay.
I keep thinking I can fly.
Like, I keep believing I can fly- AHHHHH!
Dude, I got caught on that rock!
There was nothing I could do.
Actually nothing I could do.
Wow.
Okay.
Like, what?
Guys, it's over.
Oh, oh my- Oh my god!
That's the best chest of all time!
Yeah, we got one heart.
This is...
Not great, is it?
Oh, I don't like this.
Oh, actually, I do like it.
I love it.
They stay down, right?
Okay.
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, I should probably should have taken that first.
Coupon.
Or this.
I'm gonna s- This one.
Yeah!
Gambling!
It pays off, kids!
Always do it.
Okay.
We got two hearts now.
I think we can take on the boss with this.
There's a chance he's gonna give an HP up item.
You ready?
Here we go!
It slowed down as well!
The frail and the slow.
I see where he is.
He's right there.
That bastard.
Oh, yeah.
What are you gonna do about it?
Eh?
You're nothing.
Aww!
No HP!
That's crazy.
Wait.
Oh, right.
That was the boss.
I was like, wait, there's another boss.
But no, I misread the map.
This is open.
What did that give me?
Oh god!
Oh, thank you!
Thanks, guys!
Yeah, yeah, that's fine.
You can just sit over there.
Uh, what is that?
Also, those flies are evil.
I think.
I don't like this.
These are evil flies, right?
Wait, what's happening?
Wavy cap!
Rance tears up and a slight speed down.
But causes the screen and sound to become slightly distorted?
Oh, it's an active!
This affects stacks with multiple activations, granting more stats and making everything increasingly distorted.
Nah.
I'm actually not a fan of that.
I hate it.
This was very inefficient with the bombing, I realize.
I just didn't accidentally want to pick up the item, you know?
So, it was actually kind of efficient.
If you think about it.
Genius.
Okay.
Uh, we're done here.
Moving on.
Zero bombs feels bad.
Notice, by the way, there were more floors.
Oh, wait!
We're angeling now!
Inadvertently, we have begun the angel path.
Maybe this is good for us.
Oh, no.
It's fast!
Thank God it happened in a room like this.
Also, I need to really be careful, because I am close to the brink of death!
Wow.
Gotta find a shop.
There it is!
As it gets bigger?
No thanks.
I mean, we can make things free in here, I guess.
Alright.
I'll take it.
We can actually buy this, and then make another thing free?
Hey!
Okay.
Things are gonna get ultra free now.
That's a lot of keys.
I don't care.
Oh!
Yeah, it's over!
It is over!
It's not over yet.
It is... it is over.
No HP items in the shop is just very unfortunate.
What can you do?
Oh man, this is rough.
We gotta do the boss.
Oh no!
I don't like this one at all.
Focus!
No!
I feel cheated!
I'm hanging on by a threat.
100%!
Angel now, by the way.
Oh no, hell no.
No thanks.
Ah!
I don't like this.
Wait!
There goes through there!
Spectral!
Cheers!
This is risky.
I'm not gonna do it.
It's too risky.
Wait, hold on.
I'm gonna do something here.
I just don't trust myself.
I don't.
Oh no.
What is he doing?
I don't like this.
Toy!
There we go.
Oh!
There's a pill in there.
Can't get it though.
Okay, we have to go through here.
Dude!
Oh my god.
Kill it!
We're doing that again.
Honestly, guys, I just got fucked by the item descriptions.
I thought it said, you know, good pills.
Instead it was bad pills.
It was bad pills.
That's the only reason that happened.
Hey, we got a buffer already.
Sweet.
What?
Okay, there we go.
That guy had HP.
I mean, this challenge is easy as hell, okay?
There's no way...
Like, it was just a very unfortunate set of circumstances in that last run.
I had no control of it.
Ooh, shot speed.
Nice.
I actually really like this one.
Bait him!
There we go.
I saw that.
My shots are also kind of bending a little bit.
I don't like that part.
Like a hidden effect.
Interesting shot.
What was this one?
Not feeling it.
Yeah, I don't know.
The...
Shot speed increase here.
It's not...
It's just something...
It feels off.
You know?
Something about it doesn't feel right.
But I guess the net effect is still positive.
Oh, this is gonna be easy.
That...
That was nice.
Increases damage.
Oh, it's a double trouble!
Wombo combo!
Okay.
Heed'n.
Easy, easy.
Latch key.
Oh, yeah.
Um...
Yes.
Oh!
Don't mind if I do.
I also have a bomb.
I could get the chest.
Probably a bomb inside the chest, right?
Let's get ready here.
Oi!
Hohoho!
Look at that!
Glad I didn't use the bomb!
Boy, am I glad.
Oh, this one is a...
Wait, what?
There's no way in.
Oh, no!
Bro, I need flying.
Right now.
Man, that's a...
That's like...
The massivest blue ball of all time.
Uh...
Yeah...
Okay.
I'll do it.
I'll buy it.
Ah!
Ah...
Bad idea.
Hi!
I knew it!
Hey, we got a bomb!
I'm gonna use that bomb.
Somewhere.
There was a place where it made sense.
Where was it?
In fact, there's multiple places.
There's a place up here with a golden chest.
I think I like that more.
They have better rewards, right?
Alright.
Not amazing.
Let's go.
This was totally worth...
Like, everything that happened on this floor was incredible.
From start to finish.
Easy challenge.
Easy.
We're definitely doing Fight Club.
God, I love this item so much!
Okay, well...
That's just...
plain unfortunate.
I was in the corner.
You know...
I'm actually gonna get rid of this thing.
Cause it's shit now.
I don't like having it.
Huh?
Just an empty room?
Holy shit!
Ah, it feels so good.
That's a steam sale.
Intriguing.
Ah...
Something's gonna come out of the ground?
No?
Okay.
God, I...
It's been a while since we had this...
Brimstone.
How...
I have missed you.
Oh my...
God.
HP, HP!
Yes!
Nice.
That is mega huge.
I am gonna go ahead and say that there is no way I lose this run.
It should be physically impossible to lose this run.
And if I do lose this run...
I will punish myself.
That's right.
I will have hot dogs for dinner tonight if that happens.
And ice cream afterwards.
Okay, let's go north.
And get...
Out...
Of here.
Wait, why is that second floor like...
Uh...
Weirdly...
Oh, is it because we had a double trouble?
Probably.
100% demon.
But we have no buffer.
Huh.
Weird room.
Sweet.
We're gonna have a battery for later if...
We find something.
Like an active.
Arcade.
No thanks.
Look at them growing tomatoes in here.
I think we do it.
We gotta go fast here.
Hopefully not get hit.
Never mind.
I legit forgot what this boss did.
But as soon as I got hit, I was like, oh yeah, right.
That's what he does.
There's still 1% chance, guys.
1%.
Too bad.
Wait, that's useless for me.
I don't need range.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Hey, wait a sec.
Money.
Let's go find a shop then.
Should I or should I not?
I'm gonna do it.
Copy's hit?
Oh!
What the...
No!
Ah!
I'm not ready for this!
Just kill him fast!
Oh my god.
Wait, does that even work for me?
Hey, it does!
Not bad.
Alright.
I'm not too unhappy about that then.
Oh!
Satisfying.
Maybe actually worth it.
If you think about it, it's like a better blood donation.
Wait, oh!
This room.
Oh, 4 is the one I don't know.
Hold on.
I think at least.
Let me see.
I...
Yeah, I don't know what...
This does.
What...
What is happening when I do this?
It...
I...
Yeah, I don't know.
Huh.
Like, I feel like I should at least be able to notice something is off, but I've never noticed anything.
I'm gonna do this.
Huh?
Algus?
Gains invincibility bubble for 20 seconds.
I've never seen that.
That's crazy.
Does it mean I can't attack at the same time though?
Because if that's the case, then I'm not too happy.
No, it's a fake shop!
Ah...
That sucks.
Hate the fake shops.
Yeah, you know what?
Since we're so rich, we can go arcade.
Let's do this.
Give me a buffer.
Whoa.
Uh...
Maybe I'll use that.
Huh?
Chance of getting the scatoll effect?
Yeah, why not?
Oh, wait a sec.
This one is interesting.
Hey, I like that!
Do I like that?
Yeah, I like it.
What?
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa!
Hold on!
Oh, that doesn't do anything.
That's too bad.
That's what I was looking for.
A buffer.
More blue hearts.
Lies.
Uh...
No thanks.
Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Uh...
Chests and pickups.
Ah, these are all trinkets.
So it doesn't work here.
Oh.
When blue flies are spawned...
Oh!
Joe!
That's a crazy combination!
We're guppying today!
I'm moving on with this.
Holy shit!
Let's fight room.
I can't see my HP.
That's unfortunate.
Oh my god, we're gonna have so many flies!
It's going to be wild!
In the pizza!
La la la la la la la la la la!
We're gonna have a party.
Uh, what's this?
Shot speed up, range down.
I like that, except it doesn't actually do anything for me.
Uh, okay.
Weird.
There's a button.
I need to press the button.
Gym.
Come on then, mom.
I mean, I'm gonna have so many flies.
The game is gonna crash!
Uh oh.
Crap.
Dude, I can't wait to smack the ball!
Oh!
What was that?
Why was the timer so low on the explosion thingy?
The fuse!
That's unfair.
I can't even see my HP.
I have no idea how bad...
How bad things are right now.
Okay, that's good though.
Hey, we still have a hundred percent demon.
That's a good sign.
Oh, this is a...
Okay.
Mega brownie!
Wait, what?
What?
I was in a panic spiral!
Fuck me, dude!
Holy shit!
Well, okay.
The thing is, I don't know what my HP status is.
I could have died just now.
Oh!
I'm so scared!
I don't know my HP!
This is so bad!
But hey, I can fly!
Oh wait, I have Algis!
I should have used that, shouldn't I?
I forgot I had it.
Oh sh...
Oh my god.
We can reroll!
PSD!
More blue flies, I like it.
Friends till the end.
Reroll.
Wait, what was this one?
Let's just spawn a...
Mmm.
Chaos.
That is a good one!
We like chaos!
I do declare.
Number two.
Taking damage fires a ring of ten large tears.
No.
Pills are good, right?
Shot speed up is bad for me.
I mean, it doesn't matter.
I could blow the thing up.
Uh, but we also...
We have a couple rooms left.
Let's just...
explore a little bit.
And also look for secrets.
I got a bunch of bombs.
Oh no.
I hate this room.
I'm actually gonna bomb some of this.
Maybe it's like here?
I gotta check from the south side.
No!
Okay, it's not there.
Could be here.
Nope.
Well, then I'm kinda out of options.
It should be in the center.
Unless...
No.
Maybe here?
Ah!
Oh, it's a fake shop!
No, it's not even a shop, is it?
Nevermind.
Hey, we needed money!
Money!
Money is good!
I actually am happy about this.
Now we go back to shop and go crazy.
We don't need this.
Let's get tall.
Many fly enemies become less dangerous.
I shall become the lord of flies.
Say...
Ooh!
Wait, wait!
Plus one health.
Shields all red hearts, homing tears.
Ooh!
Ho ho ho ho ho ho ho!
Okay, we got a buffer.
I like it.
What's that one?
Mo...
Oh, that...
It's gonna make us into a Leviathan.
Additional charged attack.
Uh...
Oh, that's the one I had last time.
No, I don't want that, actually.
Also, I'm running out of money here.
Let's just destroy it with a bomb now.
Hope for some money.
Nice!
And what do we get?
Another blue heart and poop.
I'll take the blue heart.
Thank you very much.
This was...
Incredible!
What a shop!
I gotta be careful here.
Uh...
Let's go to boss.
Oh yeah, I can fly now!
No need to worry about...
Insects anymore.
I freaking hate insects!
Also, my attack is white now.
Okay, so this is mom!
This is mom.
Wait, we only have two hearts?
What the...
What the frick just happened with my attack just now?
That's a fool card right there.
Oh, I did!
It's because of the...
It's homing!
Yo, my attack is crazy!
What the frick?
Yo!
I mean...
This is insanity.
Hello?
I'm way more powerful than I thought I was.
And I already thought I was powerful.
This is how crazy this is.
Uh...
Steven...
Nah.
Tears, range...
Random heart pickups is lovely.
I do like that.
Ayy!
There it is!
I'm taking it.
Black hearts!
Yeah!
Okay, now we go south.
Oh!
Oh, I can fly!
Heh!
Right.
Don't have to worry about this either, then.
Why did I go in here?
Money!
Equals power!
So, I don't know.
Maybe I'll save my...
Algiers for the...
Final, final fight.
And not the mom fight.
Because mom is gonna be frickin' easy.
Hello?
It's gonna be madness.
Wait, if I go in here I can't come back.
So let's just explore the rest first.
Hahahaha!
Damn!
The damage is out of control.
Everyone knows it.
Should I...
I'm gonna do it.
Nice!
It paid off!
Holy shit!
I cannot lose!
Oh!
It's fine.
It's boss time.
Get ready to face...
The danger!
Oh ho ho ho ho ho!
Wonderful.
Okay.
Scarred womb.
Fight club?
You know I do that.
What the hell is that?
Wait, is that the...
The...
The poop flinging?
I think it may be the poop flinging.
Yeah!
Aha!
Okay.
Weird that I get that now.
Mmm...
Yeah, let's...
Go in here.
Experimental pill.
That's not good for me.
This is like...
One of the most OP...
Runs I've ever had.
Like, it is insane how much damage I am doing to these fools.
But of course, it's not...
It's not the run.
It's me.
It's skill.
I am the one who's doing it.
We don't need to do anything.
Let's just go.
Who cares?
We got...
Well, we got demons.
With mom's razor?
Uh...
No.
Actually.
I don't...
I don't need that.
I'm fine.
Okay.
This is the last...
I think.
Nothing after this.
Hopefully.
Oh yeah, fly.
Haha.
I don't know how to open this door!
Like...
Legitimately, I am so...
Out of ideas.
At this point.
I have given up on trying to understand it.
Oh!
Nice.
Shot speed up.
Shot speed up!
Shot speed doesn't matter for me.
What's this?
Bob's curse.
Huh.
Man, things die fast.
Huh?
Where did that thing come from?
Here we go!
Bring it on then!
Wow!
Thank you.
Nice.
The rune of Berkano has appeared!
Okay.
Um...
Let's see here.
All the challenges are done.
Now we have ret challenges coming up.
We don't do ret today.
Next time we do challenges, we're gonna do the ret challenges.
I wanna do more runs.
Guys.
We gotta get this bad boy to five!
We gotta go five.
Who are we gonna bring?
What about Bethany?
We haven't even killed Mom.
We haven't killed Isaac.
Or Satan.
There's lots of stuff to do.
I wanna do it.
Let's do it!
I have to remind myself how this works.
Oh, I can't read about it right.
But this is the one that combines with other items and it does things.
And when you pick up Blue Hearts, it goes into her thingy and she spawns weird flies.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Oh wait, and if I use this now...
Yeah, that's right, that's right.
That's how that works.
It's like a little protective shield.
Okay.
Charm of the Vampire.
Yeah!
You know what this means, right?
This is a step run.
That is a step run right there.
Oh my...
God!
Oh, they don't count.
They become blue.
Man.
Oh yeah, I shoot more things as well the more I have of these.
True.
Forgot about that.
Damage is very low though.
Actually, it's not.
Just that I can't hit.
My aim is not great.
Okay.
I don't have a bomb.
Go!
What the?
Why was he so fast?
That was weird.
Oh!
How is anyone gonna dodge that?
Impossible!
Sometimes you get fucked by RNG like that, you know?
Lots of small enemies is good though.
Means I can heal more.
Uh...
That's a small...
Small level.
I mean, I have a free key, right?
So we may as well go into the shop.
See what's in there.
Oh wait, the shop is open.
Oh, I would love a mystery gift.
Don't have the money for it.
Shit.
Uh, Gemini is okay.
That's not too hard.
Just gotta get into a rhythm!
Oh my god.
Oh, nice!
That was a heal!
Can we get into a cheese configuration?
Look at me!
I'm playing with my food.
I am enjoying this.
Wonderful.
Sick.
More damage.
Move on.
We have a simple goal in this run, ladies and gentlemen.
We are going to kick Isaac's ass!
That's the plan.
And we can't see anything.
We're blind.
Wait!
Bethany is the one with the angel stuff!
Nice!
I'm gonna have a couple of these.
Uh, wait.
We have four doors.
So let's just, uh...
Labyrinth method.
Maze method.
That's all I get from here.
Okay.
Alright.
Should have spoken...
Should not have spoken so soon.
Oh shit, my...
God.
There goes my little companion.
When is my next heal?
Ooh.
There we go.
This actually means I should not be picking up hearts.
Not very often, because...
It's only emergencies.
If I can heal via this mechanism, that's...
That's better.
Uh, I've got three keys.
Okay.
Yeah, okay.
I'll heal.
No, I'm not.
Let's not get lazy.
We have that for later.
Even...
Dude, we're gonna step so hard.
If I get the opportunity?
Let's go in here.
Have we been there?
No, we haven't.
Okay.
More pills.
Infested.
Oh!
Okay.
Wow!
Man, that was actually so well played.
I hate this.
Yeah!
For me.
I love when you...
That sounded dirty all of a sudden, actually, now that I think about it.
It was not meant that way.
I hit him.
Uh...
Ooh!
I love...
That's actually really good for me.
Soul hearts...
Is what fuels me.
Flat penny?
Yeah.
More coins is always good.
Oh, this room is gonna be cancer.
Oh, I hate this already.
This is gonna be annoying.
One left.
Come on!
Little horn.
Oh, sick!
That was a healing.
Not that I needed it, but you know.
What the...
Wait, did he just shoot his little thingies into the flame?
And they got disappeared because of that?
I like that.
Stop making those thingies.
I don't like it when you do.
Yeah.
Throw them into the fire.
Cast it into the fire!
Blue cap.
Oh, we got angels incoming.
And we got this all.
God.
This is incredible.
Aw.
Hey!
Wait a minute.
That's actually pretty good, I guess.
Eh, that's not too bad.
I look like a proper nun now.
Like a, um...
Like a BDSM nun.
You know what I mean?
They must exist.
Okay.
Uh...
I'm not done exploring.
The thing is though, we have an eternal heart.
So maybe I am done exploring.
I don't remember if I found something already here.
Wait, what did I find here?
Oh no, I found this, didn't I?
So we have found treasure room.
Fuck this place.
We're leaving.
Yeah.
See you later!
Book of...
Denial.
That's not bad.
Shadows.
Damage nullifying shields.
That's...
I'm not really...
Ah, but wait, wait!
There's weird interactions here though.
One middle wisp, one HP...
I still don't understand this in great detail.
Wait, wisp is immune to projectile damage?
Hold on.
That seems really good.
Whoa!
Hold on.
Also, we have this now.
That's good.
I mean, that's also nice.
But...
Wisp is immune to projectile damage?
I get that the damage of the wisp is one third.
Hmm.
I don't really care about the damage nullifying shield very much.
Unless they also protect my wisps.
I gotta try it.
Wait, let me see.
Does that animation disappear?
No?
Okay, okay.
So...
So that guy has a shield on right now, and he's gonna be immune to a projectile.
But I guess he's still gonna disappear if I run into somebody.
But here's what I can do.
I can spawn a bunch with this thing.
And then switch.
And maybe come back.
This is getting exciting, actually.
So wait, does that mean my wisps are gonna block damage still, though?
They are?!
Oh my god!
That means that animal is out of control!
I have to go get it.
We need more of this.
Love animals.
I'm in a corner!
Fuck!
I lost my angel!
Nice.
Why didn't I do it in here?!
You know what?
Nah, fuck this one.
I don't like it.
We're taking the other one.
I'm just gonna get a couple more of these flies first.
Uh...
Perhaps he'll give me some blue hearts.
That's my hope.
What the...
Frickin' artillery!
There we go, we got...
Two now.
Okay.
Not falling for that.
Oh my...
God!
What?!
Oi yoi yoi.
Let's go to Fight Club.
Uh, may as well step in here now.
Oh, is that the hand?
Yeah!
I like that one.
Actually...
No.
I wanna pick up more money.
Especially with the bum friend.
What's that?
I can't read it during combat.
Let's see.
Hey, that's actually...
Uh...
Not too bad.
Very nice.
In fact, I want this money.
I don't want this bum friend to pick up the money just yet.
Maybe when I'm rich he can do it, but...
Right now, no.
The money is mine.
Very nice!
The higher effect.
Love that.
I...
I need to do it in combat!
Why am I like this?
Oh, it doesn't matter.
We got 27 coins in LeBanco.
We got a...
Ooh, that's a Coupono!
How does that interact with my thingy?
One middle wisp, two HP, three...
Triple shot?
Wait!
Wisps are destroyed when anything is purchased!
Eee!
Hmm...
Maybe I'll do the boss before...
Oh...
Yeah.
Boss first, then we come back.
I guess.
Wait, it's only when I buy things it's destroyed, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Aww...
But wait!
Taking this is technically not buying it!
Heh heh!
Good.
Good!
What is this bag here?
Spawn a sack.
Coins have a chance to be converted to a sack?
It's actually not...
Bad?
You know what?
Let me pick this up.
Walk around a bit more.
And...
You know...
Get some energy on that.
I do like it.
I don't think we can get too much more energy, though.
Actually, we can.
No, we can't.
Mega fatty.
This is the jumping jack.
We gotta jump!
Holy shit.
Oi
oi!
Ho!
Oh my...
Okay, well, at least my flies are getting destroyed so that now I can buy from the shop.
PJs.
Let's go back.
This run is weird so far.
I don't know.
It's...
Weird.
I could use the coupon right now.
But that's gonna consume, I think, four blue hearts.
Not great.
Maybe I say fuck the coupon.
Dude, what if...
I just do this?
And I take this?
Should I keep the coupon?
Hold on.
I don't know.
I kinda wanna get the other book, honestly.
Like, it's nice to have, you know, the ranged shields, I guess, but...
Just damage, you know?
We need it.
I don't have a lot of it.
Three bombs?
Let's look for a secret.
I suspect maybe one here.
Or down here somewhere.
Okay, so it's not there.
That's good to know.
There.
What?!
Okay.
Oi!
The bomb friend almost took the...
the tenor.
Imagine if that happened.
I mean, I may as well use it, right?
When there's battery on it.
Oh, wait a minute.
Don't I have the thing that takes me to multiple...
stages of battery?
No.
I got confused because I think that the blue heart effect, you know?
Okay, I think it's over here on the left.
Yeah, that looks good so far.
Right there.
Yes!
Now I've got money again.
I completely forgot what was in the shop.
Oh, yeah.
I'll take this.
Ah, should I take this?
No.
I'll keep what I have.
I like the one I have.
Need the damage, right?
Let's-a go!
I'm happy with this run.
I got almost 50% angel chance now.
That...
That didn't just happen.
All my hard work gone in approximately 1.7 seconds.
Ah, I should have used it before I went in, but...
Actually, I should have used it in the next room.
I am so bad at timing my active.
It's crazy.
Fuck.
And now I'm stuck in a corner!
Hate being stuck in a corner.
A little bit out of- actually, I should use this now.
I'm so bad.
Don't you dare pick that up.
He went for it, you saw that, right?
He was trying to get it.
Hey, we got a bunch of bombs.
Inanimate object!
It's gone.
Nice.
That's exactly what we needed.
Damage is good.
I still don't know if damage actually scales my...
My little flies.
Or wisps.
Oh my goodness.
No, bomb friend!
It got painted into the enemy because of my bomb friend.
Well, that's crap.
That's really bad.
We gotta have at least one speed.
That's like a rule.
If you're below one speed, you're fat.
And you can't really dodge things.
Yeah, dude, I'm happy about this so far.
This is- this is some good damage now.
A butt penny?
No.
Crap.
Did my angel just go away there?
Shit.
Oh my god.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Fuck!
Well, my angel didn't go down.
So I guess it's stuck at 15 now.
I overreacted for no reason.
I feel like these are some crazy rooms I'm getting here.
Yeah.
There's a very low chance of angel, but it's there.
The chance is there.
Right, you do that.
That was very easy.
Wow.
Good damage here.
Let's go.
I feel good.
This run slaps.
We're getting to...
...a streak of five!
Can you feel it?
I feel it.
It's coming.
No, don't.
Thank you, dude!
Thank you.
I'm scared of the laser.
Wait, the- both worms died?
Wow.
Too risky I think.
Let's wait with the Fight Club until we've found the boss.
Yeah, this room is gonna kill me.
Yeah, there's no way I can avoid damage here.
Boss dreams!
Bye-bye.
I meant angel.
I misclicked.
Save that heart.
There we go.
Virgo!
Uh...
Yeah!
We're gonna be pill-maxing.
Oh, no.
What is this room?
Wow!
Oh!
Please!
Oh, my God.
I never stood a chance.
Yeah, I don't know.
Fucking hell.
Oh, this is rough.
I'm experiencing some turbulence.
Six, six, six.
Oh, God.
Ah!
There we go.
Fucking hell.
Who the fuck puts the keybite on F?
Hello?
Right next to WASD?
What were you smoking when you decided that?
Unbelievable.
Like, can we be real here?
Like, hello?
F?
Of all keys on the entire keyboard?
How often do you have to switch size?
I don't understand.
Slash rant.
We got a blue map.
I actually love this one.
Therefore, I buy it.
No, I...
See, I'm not gonna take this because then I'm not gonna get my pills.
And mommy needs pills.
Oh, yeah.
Ooh.
Ah.
Hehehehe.
Trying to steal this.
Don't even think about it.
Nope.
They're mine.
I need these points.
Crazy room!
God, they're so dumb looking.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wow.
Guys, we're gonna go for a maximum stepping session.
This is actually ideal stepping scenarios.
Oh, wait.
That's actually hurting quite a bit.
I thought it was half a heart for some reason.
I'll go heal up a little bit.
Also, I'm super slow.
I need some speed.
This is gonna be full of hearts.
Oh, well.
Hey, this guy wants bombs?
I can give him bombs.
I like the atmosphere in here.
It's very cozy.
I would spend a couple hours in here.
That's right.
Keep healing me.
Let's barter.
Actually, maybe I'll let this guy take some money now.
I have 43.
Dankeschön.
You know what?
Actually, let's go to the curse room.
That's a good investment of time.
I really should be activating this.
As soon as the battery is full.
Nah, it's too risky.
Can't do it.
Can I get to full health?
Because then we can actually go into Fight Club.
I don't think so.
I should have thought of that before I did this.
But you're still rooms we haven't explored.
Well, in that case...
I feel like I lost all my skills in the span of 30 minutes.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm playing so bad.
I can't explain it.
Yeah, I'm leaving.
Get the hell out of here.
I'm not even gonna...
You know what?
Let's donate.
I have so much money.
Ah!
That's good.
Now we leave.
Oof!
I mean, it's going pretty well.
It just doesn't feel like it is, you know?
It's a weird contrast.
In my brain.
The battery.
Man, he sounds angry.
Look at that.
You know what?
You can have the coins.
Take some coins.
Thanks.
Wait, how am I getting up there?
There has to be like a weird roundabout way then.
Via here.
I feel like I'm perpetually stuck on 17.
In...
I was about to say, if you pick up a fiver, you're gonna give me something good.
But it doesn't look like it.
Yeah.
Actually.
Well, we have a teleport now in case we want to use that.
Hmm.
I don't think I will.
We have a simple objective here.
I'm gonna stick to it.
Take the coin.
And go into the next secret room.
Oh, we have a shot speed up.
Wow.
Shot speed up.
Tears!
Yay!
That's a good amount of tears right there.
And bomb taker.
Hey!
Good deal, bomb.
Give me an item.
Hot bombs.
Wow.
Grants immunity to damage from stationary fires.
Okay.
Sure.
This guy wants coins.
Uh, yeah.
Why not?
I'll give him a couple.
No, actually.
Let's wait for the shop.
See what's in there.
I hate this room.
This is gonna be...
Oh my god.
Uh, 62% demon.
We gotta find the boss.
Oh no.
Wow.
I didn't mean to use it.
I missed...
Ah, that goes to the angel.
Angel!
I will never get my angel.
It is incredibly difficult when you can't get a buffer.
Man, this extra tier stat here is really helping.
Feels good.
Blow it.
Hello.
That's a stepper.
Please let me find a step room.
This is the perfect setup.
Grant me this one wish.
Fuck, I forgot its mom!
Oh no!
Great.
Shit balls.
We have no way of leaving either.
Well, that was honestly very smooth.
That was really... Wait, why is a demon appearing?
Where's my angel?
I guess I do have a lot of red hearts.
Maybe it's...
You know what?
Okay.
Let's demonize.
Guppy's paw.
Wait.
Times three middle wisps.
20 HP.
3.5 damage.
Definitely not that one.
Hmm.
Bro, I don't like this.
What is this?
Magician.
Okay, that's pretty good, I guess.
Ah.
I can't go back.
Oh!
What a blunder.
Shit!
We're gonna salvage it.
It's fine.
Yeah.
It is not gonna affect...
The angel chance.
Oh yeah.
It's take...
It's taking a whole...
HP now when I do that.
I'm going towards the secret rooms.
What are you up to?
Open up your tummy.
Really?
Just three damage?
That's kinda crazy, isn't it?
For a trinket?
Alright.
I'll take it.
Oh my...
God.
I'm approaching the secrets.
Man, these guys are tangy.
Hello?
Oh.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Ah.
Ancient recall.
Chariot.
Magician.
I'll take this.
Wasn't there an HP in here?
I need some extra speed.
I feel...
I'm just too slow.
You know, that's why I keep running into enemies and shit.
I just...
I just can't...
Like this.
Can't dodge protectiles.
Bad.
Oh.
Seven percent angel.
Oh wait.
This is...
Uh...
Wait.
How?
Give me hearts.
Or pills.
This is always poops.
Hey, I've got 18...
Uh...
Keys.
I can give him some.
Okay.
Another one?
The lovers.
Beggar.
Judgment.
Hmm.
Ansus!
Use it now.
Okay, so the...
I can't see shit.
Boss is down there.
Okay.
Let's just go.
I feel good.
I do.
Uh, secret.
Let's do that.
Ooh.
We come back for that.
Because we can't go back on this boss.
We're not gonna be locked somewhere.
Actually use this.
Up the...
Man.
I thought they were deactivated.
I was done with the...
Room.
I wonder why that is, by the way.
Some rooms just don't deactivate when they're done.
Others do.
It's...
I don't understand the logic.
Uh...
You might wanna join me out here, or...
Thank you.
Piddlesticks.
Okay.
Before I leave...
Eternal heart.
Can't believe how many red hearts we have.
Ah, wait, wait.
We haven't even found treasure room!
Brother man.
We are not done here.
But...
Wait.
Didn't we do ANSYS?
How come that is not revealed?
I'm confused about this.
Also, what is this thing over there?
Something is off here.
This is like a disturbance in the force.
My senses are tingling.
Uh...
Is it because we're in the womb?
Oh god.
Okay.
Here we go!
Do not fuck this up.
Go!
Nice.
Further we go.
Now it's time for...
It lives.
And I've got keys up the wazoo.
Justice!
Very nice.
Dude, these are some sick chests!
What the...
Holy shit!
I've yet to have, like, a bunch of flies with me.
Have you noticed?
Like, this run is kinda...
Flyless.
Usually you have more flies on this character.
Fuck me.
I will never get an angel.
I WILL NEVER GET AN ANGEL!
I don't even know what I'm doing.
I'm flabbergasted.
I am...
Annoyed and...
Perturbed.
I don't even know what just happened.
I feel like Bethany is kind of a hard character to play.
Because you don't get any buffers.
Fucking took my fly away!
I can't keep a fly more...
Like, I can only keep one fly at a time, it seems.
Before it disappears.
I need, like, an active item that only has one charge.
So I can get a fly every single room, you know?
Wait, what?
Oh.
Thanks.
Oh, I should've gone for the secret first.
Get him, bomb!
Hey!
Thanks!
That's actually pretty good.
Geez, for me...
I'm fully healed now?
Still have Magician on...
Standby here.
Come on.
Do something amazing.
Shot speed up.
Uh...
I don't want this.
Nice.
Wait, three...
Okay, hold on.
Is there a step room?
Because if there's a step room, this is going to go hard.
This is like the ultimate stepper.
If I've ever seen one.
Nice.
We gotta find a step room.
It has to exist.
Also...
When I use my book...
Now hold on a second.
I need to test something.
So I'm at 14 damage now.
Okay, so my baseline is 11.
Got it.
He wants coins.
And you know what?
I'm gonna give it to him.
Because there's no more shops anyway.
Give me something nice.
What do I want from him?
Yeah, stuff like that is good, I guess.
Hey!
I should not have picked that up yet.
Oh good, it doesn't fully heal.
Okay, then it's good.
I thought it was gonna fully heal me.
We even have healing in here.
Wow, this is a stepper, guys.
Ultimate steppage.
If only we can get a step room.
I don't want to actually have this fly run into my flies here.
Oh!
Ooh!
Flies are my friends.
Give me that one.
Come on, stepp room!
I know you're here!
Wait, what?
Do I even...
Wait, do I even want a stepp room?
I'm trying to...
Like, why am I chasing a stepp room anyway?
I guess it's gonna give...
It's gonna give me keys, I guess.
Angels.
But I don't really need money, which is like one of the big reasons to do it.
Why am I doing this?
Also, there is no stepp room, so...
Doesn't matter.
Let's go get that healing.
Let's do it.
I am ready.
It lives!
Yes, mom.
What is it, mom?
You unlock the wisp, baby?
Nice.
We're going up, because I'm gonna slap Isaac's ass.
It's gonna be like...
You'll see.
It's gonna be glorious.
I hate being lost, especially in a place like this.
That is no bueno.
Wait, I'm gonna move to stationary fires.
Yeah, I am.
Damn right I am.
That is a suspicious pot, I was about to say!
I don't trust like that.
Oh my god, there's flies.
And there goes my angel!
Wait, did I even have an angel?
What the hell is all this?
Wheel of Fortune, yeah, okay.
This is actually good.
A hermit.
Useless.
The moon.
Not useless!
Maybe I should see what this is.
Oh, it's hematemesis.
Oh, no.
Ah-ha!
Uh...
I keep giving it money.
I'm using all my money.
Never mind, I got money again!
Way!
Actually insane.
So, so, what have we got here?
We got, uh, broken remote.
I don't like that, actually.
No.
I don't want that.
I'm good!
Look at these magicians.
Oh, the lost here is just so bad.
Only one way to go, though, so...
That's something.
Oh my...
God!
Goddamn.
Oh, this is not healing.
Wait, what is this?
These enemies are very rare.
You almost never see them.
We're gonna let, uh, the bomb pick up all the money now.
Just for the chance of him dropping some health.
Every 15 shots...
Oh!
I like this one, actually!
This is a good one!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Aww.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten...
That's close enough.
Holy...
Did I get hit just now?
This is especially good now that I have high tiers, you know?
This is nice.
Oh, I'm blind!
Can't see anyway!
Ugh, stop...
Erratic movements.
I'm still gonna slap Isaac, though.
It's not even gonna be close.
Like, you may look at this and go, this is not going well.
It's not, but Isaac is so easy.
It doesn't even matter.
Unless he's like the modified version where he goes crazy.
Guess we'll have to see.
Wait, is...
What is he...
Oh, my...
My guy is picking up coins.
Ah!
How the fuck did that happen?
Insane.
Woah.
Die!
Give me something good.
Huh?
Wait, there's more in here.
Someone is flapping.
Yay!
Not bad.
Oh, that's nice.
Is it better than three damage, though?
Wait a sec.
There's something wrong here.
Gain damage for the...
Hold up!
How is my damage 11.69 right now?
I don't know.
There...
There's something going on here that doesn't make any sense.
At all.
Because earlier, the baseline was 11 damage.
And that was after...
The...
The damage up card wore off.
But I still had the trinket on.
So what the hell?
Wait, how's my damage 11?
Should it be 14 right now?
Wait, what...
What is happening?
No, my damage is 8?!
Ah!
I don't understand what's happening!
Give me this.
Oh, my God.
I don't know what is going on right now.
Give me that.
Ideally, I would find some kind of active item now that...
Where it's...
Wait, can I actually...
Can I stack the damage from this in one room?
Let's say I use this book of damage multiple times.
Am I gonna get multiple damage?
I guess I'll find out...
During the boss fight...
Uh-oh.
Yeah!
And...
Gyo-nice!
Meow.
Actually a professional gamer.
Uh...
Where's the boss?
Is...
Are you in here?
Hohohoho!
I think I explored that path fully.
Dude, I hate not having a map.
It is just such an annoying debuff.
To me, that doesn't bring any fun at all.
It's not a fun debuff, you know?
There we go.
Oh.
Ah.
Little rascals.
Wait, how am I gonna... Yo, this guy is super annoying!
What do you do in this room if you don't have bombs?
Are you cooked?
Another one here.
Wait, where's all the healing at?
Okay, here we go.
I'm going in, I'm gonna go drowsy, and I'm gonna stack the shit up on this Book of Denial.
Oh, we can stack it!
Okay, I'm not gonna stack it fully.
This is definitely more than enough.
This is insane.
Somehow I got hit.
Oh, it's the ultimate version of Isaac.
Oh, okay, that's a bad idea.
Why am I shooting slow here?
There we go.
That was easy.
I set out to do what I wanted.
And we're done.
Wait!
Right.
I keep forgetting what's down in this fucking box!
What is in this box?
What's in this box?
Oh, okay.
So when you go in this... When you go in the box, the door with the key is there!
Fuck it.
Fuck me.
Finger!
I hate that.
Maggie?
Mm.
These are horrible items!
Bozo!
Uh... I like that one.
That's okay.
Spawns the item displayed in the jars icon.
Yeah?
And what's that gonna be?
Spawns a random wisp!
Interesting.
Oh, but 12 charges!
Eww.
I guess I can use it once.
I don't know what that icon is.
Oh, shit.
Oh, okay.
Give me that one.
Uh...
Wait, where's my... Oh, there it is.
I guess I may as well take this, right?
No reason not to take it.
Alright.
We got secrets here as well.
Very good.
Uh, let's go in here.
Oh!
I didn't mean to destroy that.
I think the finger did it.
It wasn't me.
Okay.
Spawn something good for me.
I'll come back for that.
If I need it.
So many red hearts!
This is actually really good.
I also forgot what boss is at the end of this.
No, it's the...
Delirium.
I keep thinking of the other one.
The fat one.
Oh, shit.
Oh my god, please.
I'm getting fucking gangbanged into corners here!
Give me that healing.
Yeah.
Fill me up.
Wait, that...
I didn't mean it like that.
I meant, like, the hell.
It's just...
When it came after that sentence I said earlier, you know, it's...
Could be misconstrued a little bit.
Dude, I'm a big fan of the pencil.
I do like it.
Pick up the money.
I have way too many...
Things.
I just wanna let go of them and move to Nipol, you know?
Nothing.
Oh, we got boss here!
Use this.
Alright, let's go.
Take me home!
Oh!
Wait, no!
It's this guy!
Right!
Oh, shit.
Oh my god.
Oh, yeah.
We have a shield.
Wait, why don't we have a shield?
Ah, greedy.
That was greedy.
Yeah, so when we go down there, that's delirium.
That's delirium.
And I'm going.
The blessed penny has appeared.
I'm still unlocking frickin' new items and I've played this game for I don't even know how many hours.
How?
Like, it's crazy.
Let's see.
Oh, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
Ah, we don't... no.
No way.
That's never gonna happen, is it?
Yeah, I'm not getting anywhere near those...
...objects over there.
Are you coming this way?
Oh!
Yeah, dude!
Delirium!
It's gonna be slowium!
Oh, I hate that I can't see my HP.
This is a big problem.
This is gonna pose big challenges.
Where the hell are they?
God, they're annoying!
Hey, come here!
Finally.
But this is the...
The one where it's like random bosses.
Monstro, okay.
That's cool.
What the hell is hitting me?!
Oh, it's a little... stupid fly.
Yo, sick!
We get to see all the boss rooms!
That is actually amazing.
I wonder if we can somehow see which one is delirium.
Is there a change in size or something?
Doesn't look like it.
Shit.
Okay.
It's still a gamble.
Wait, what?!
Oh!
I thought I could go further down.
Here we go!
That's a random card.
Oh yeah, but cards are pills!
No, wait.
That's not how that works.
Is it?
Wait, I'm confused.
No!
Temp- No, Temperance.
Right, okay.
I'm a little confused.
It's okay.
I'm just going straight for the bosses.
I don't even care about the other rooms.
Yes, I do.
Because that's gonna lead me to the boss.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14.
I am ready with the big gun.
Triaknit!
Boom!
That was a massive shotgun right to the face.
What?
Yo, wait a minute!
Dude, the rainbow is actually insane!
When I have this much red heart health, right?
Chance- Yeah, whatever.
When does that trigger again?
Bozo.
Chance to spawn a rainbow poop on the ground when taking damage.
Okay.
Oh, crap.
Oh, man.
I couldn't find the button.
I shouldn't have- That was a waste.
Okay, here we go.
Wish me luck.
I'm drowsy.
Hey, I'm glad I took the rainbow before this.
That's going to be a big help.
Where is this- Oh, he's there.
Mom?
Wait, what?
Oh, right.
He metamorphosizes and fantasizes.
I'm gonna dye his hair.
If you know what I mean.
I'm totally gonna do this guy's nails.
What's that?
The moon?
No, thank- Wait, what?
What's happening?
Pick up the health.
I'm not even hitting anything.
Bro, this is insane!
Dude, let's activate more damage.
Let's go crazy with the damage.
Here we go.
Look at this.
There he is.
The thing is though, all my flies are gonna disappear fast.
Yeah, there's no way I can avoid them getting hit by this.
The shotgun is actually gonna end up being the most damage I do.
That right there is big.
No, my flies!
Ahhhh!
Why did I go that way?
Mistakes were made.
Okay, I'm just gonna have to accept I'm not gonna have flies.
It's fine.
He's getting very angry, it seems.
Where the hell are you?
Wish I could see my HP.
I have no idea how well it's going.
Because I can't see my HP.
Oh my...
Go-
I gotta get out of that corner!
Dude, it's weirdly...
Just as hard in slow motion.
It's like when it's full speed, it's like I'm in a flow, you know?
Here it's weird.
I have to- I- there's too much time to think, you know?
Which means I'm overthinking.
I'm not acting on God instinct.
But I think net effect is still that it's better.
Fuck.
What the hell was that?
That is like impossible to dodge.
Also, where's the rainbow poops at?
They should be spawning.
UGH!
Hit him!
This was some good dam- this is good damage.
Oh my- You just spawned on top of me!
Where are you?
Shotgun?
Come on.
I gotta- I- I-
Holy crap!
You scared me!
Oh no!
Get up there!
This is insane!
What the fuck?
UGH!
Where is this guy?
We got him!
Oh!
Jesus Christ!
Get me the hell out of here!
I can't lose!
The Star of Bethlehem has appeared.
Let's call it there.
Another successful, undefeated run by the way.
Wait, is it?
No, I failed one challenge.
One challenge I failed.
But it- it was kind of unfair, because, you know, it wasn't my fault.
Pretty much.
I would say so.
Okay, guys.
Am I the GOAT or what?
We are at a streak of five!
Can we make it to ten?
In the long run?
You think so?
If I just take it slow, right?
And- and I really think about things in every run.
No?
Come on.
You gotta believe in me.
I mean, it's- it's- it's- it's literally just me having to decide.
Whether or not I want the ten win streak.
Because I- I write the scripts, you know?
I could just tell my guy to- or at least I, you know, manage the guys who write the scripts.
How do you do the drop sound?
Um...
It's like, you make a short whistle...
and then you modulate the sound...
by, uh...
you know, using your little finger...
on your cheek.
Like this.
I'm pretty good at it at this point.
It takes a little bit of practice.
But not too much practice.
You can probably do it after, like, an afternoon of practicing.
I can even do it without the finger.
It- it- it doesn't have the same impact, though.
Let me try.
Yeah, see?
It's kinda weak.
What is the hardest thing you had to do in games?
Uh...
I don't know, actually.
Some parts of Rain World are still...
embedded in my mind.
Rain World is the first game I sort of think of.
No, Moog is, uh...
Yeah, okay, Moog was difficult.
But I was also a stubborn bitch.
I mean, I could have chosen to come back being more powerful.
I just- I was being stubborn.
I easily could have made that easier for myself, you know?
So, I don't know.
I wouldn't quite count that as a hard one.
I was just being stubborn.
But I- I have to say StarCraft II probably.
Trying to get into Grandmaster League in StarCraft II.
If you can do that, you have ascended in life.
You're like a next level human being.
To me, that's just as impressive as someone who is like...
over 2,000 in chess.
That- that stuff to me blows my brain.
Like, I- I would never be able to get to 2,000...
ELO in chess.
You're scared of Rain World?
I mean, it's okay.
The thing is, Rain World is brutal.
It's not actually that difficult.
If you have a mindset where you just think, okay, I'm gonna fuck it up.
I'm gonna have to start over and...
try different...
methods.
Then you're gonna get through it.
It's a mindset thing.
Most of all.
There are some really brutal...
situations in that game where you just...
you know, it breaks your brain.
So if you can handle the mental part of it, you can definitely beat the game.
Are you dropping Isaac soon with the third MC season?
No, like I said, I was gonna keep playing Isaac for a long time.
Right now, I don't...
see a future where I'm not playing Isaac.
It's probably gonna be a lot...
well, the cadence is gonna be a lot smaller, right?
But still.
I'll do it once in a while.
Because I do get that itch, you know?
To do a couple runs.
I've not played Deadlock recently.
I actually installed it on Steam.
Just two days ago or so.
Because I was thinking about getting back into it.
But I have yet to boot the game.
But maybe I'll do it.
I know it's come a long way.
They... they patched it...
I mean, even back when I was playing it, there were like almost daily patches.
And as far as I understand it, it's still like that.
So, it's crazy.
What competitive games have I played?
I have played StarCraft 2...
Counter-Strike, Valorant, Dota 2...
What else?
I guess Battlefield.
I wouldn't really call those competitive games.
They're like multiplayer online games.
Never played Call of Duty, actually.
Never played any fighting games.
Never played any racing games.
Except Need for Speed 2.
That shit is one of the best games I've ever played.
Maybe I am secretly into racing games, you know?
But Need for Speed Underground 2 was...
Chef's Kiss.
Especially the soundtrack.
Did you like the Red Dead series, Jibby?
I mean, I guess you did since you finished it.
It's a good game.
It's actually kind of a masterpiece.
Loved it?
Nice.
Red Dead 2 is coming in the future at some point.
I'm definitely playing with the second one at some point.
Uh, I'm not gonna look at the new Minecraft updates before getting into Create.
I actually, uh...
Just installed, uh...
Jenny.
Along with something called RLCraft, I think.
That's what I'm going with, I believe.
Someone told me that was a good combo?
Dude, I'm scared of Googling JennyMod.
Like, the way people are reacting...
I'm imagining it's some really...
Like, it's not vanilla sexual...
It's like some disturbed sexual stuff, you know?
Something where...
Something you would never tell your mom about.
It's not...
Disturbing?
Okay.
Hahahaha...
I literally can't activate it.
Maybe I'll make an OnlyFans where I sit...
And play...
Hahahaha...
I'm not gonna do that.
That would be funny though.
Wouldn't it be funny to open an OnlyFans account and just post normal gameplay videos?
Like, nothing weird about it.
Reminds me of, uh...
At some point, maybe ten years ago, I heard about this guy...
Who, uh...
Would upload lectures...
To Pornhub, you know?
He would just be explaining statistics.
On Pornhub.
Like...
It's just hilarious.
I don't know...
I don't know if it was statistics, but it was something like that, you know?
And he just had a whole series.
And that's just that.
And there were comments, you know, asking questions and stuff.
That's funny as hell.
Uh, remember when you were talking about the game Off?
And how you would be beating Off Blind?
No, I don't actually remember that.
But it sounds like something you could easily fall into.
If the game is called Off.
Some people make bank...
Bank uploading gaming videos to the hub they pay so well.
I... really?
You're joking, right?
How does that even work?
Really?
Should I open...
Like, should I actually start cross-posting to Pornhub?
Nah, you're lying.
I mean...
Yes, I'm interested.
If I could just cross-post my videos to Pornhub and earn more money?
Sure.
I would do it.
Haha, wouldn't you?
The pay-per-view is higher?
Okay.
Yeah, maybe.
But who watches that stuff on Pornhub?
Doesn't even make sense.
Open a channel in Chinese YouTube.
Oh, you mean Bilibili?
I don't know if I actually...
can do that.
I would definitely not be...
eligible for...
a monetized account there, I don't think.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean...
I'm never gonna do that.
The Pornhub thing.
I think it was a Minecraft video with some guy's parents arguing in the background on the hump.
Hmm.
Hey, Dintude!
Oh my god, I wanted to call you Dude, but Dintude.
Hey Oliver, just want to thank you for accompanying me through the last months.
Started with Minecraft and was curious about Out of Wild type on the channel.
Naturally played it before watching Let's Play and it's so nice.
Hypothesis and humor, you're one of a kind.
Thank you for being yourself.
Thank you for your comments.
I appreciate it, man.
And thank you for your sub.
That's six months now.
Half a year!
I'm actually so happy...
that you started to play Out of Wilds because you saw my videos.
Or you saw that I played it.
I want more people to play Out of Wilds, you know?
So whenever that happens, I'm always so pleased.
Same with some other games.
For example...
Ghost.
From...
Well, he's on the channel.
He writes a lot of comments.
He's been donating and, you know, gifting subs on Twitch and stuff, but...
He had never played XCOM.
And he saw that I played XCOM and now he started it and now he's addicted to it.
I love that.
I want people to get addicted to XCOM because it is truly...
such a magnificent game.
Like, holy shit.
That game is...
a freaking masterpiece.
I've never seen gameplay like that before.
They hit like a sweet spot of...
like an itch I didn't even know I had.
If you haven't played XCOM, you have to play it.
XCOM is crazy good.
It's so addicting.
So please play it if you haven't.
I have seen something about the game Amori.
I've seen the poster of it.
I'm seeing this...
this boy in like a white shirt with blue stripes or something, right?
But that's all.
It's on my backlog.
Speaking of...
The backlog got a huge update, guys.
You should totally go visit it.
There's a new design and the rankings have been updated with a very...
very advanced statistical backbone now.
So what I've done basically, and so far it's almost 1500 comparisons, I have simply been choosing one game that I like more than the others.
So it's gonna present two games, you know?
Out of Wilds or Minecraft.
And then I pick one of them, the one I like the most, or I click tie.
You know?
And I do that 1500 times and a very advanced statistical model figures out my actual likes.
So you can even go in and look at that.
There's statistics about it.
It's pretty cool.
Did you code this?
Yeah.
I mean, with the help of Fable, obviously.
Bit of Fable, a bit of Opus.
Claude has gotten to the point where it is significantly better than me at coding.
Like, I can't even get close to the quality of the code that it writes.
It's really humbling in a way.
It's like, damn.
I guess this is it now, huh?
That was it.
No more manual writing code.
It's over.
It's so over.
I'm a 5.6 soul boy now.
Are you?
I haven't tried it.
I heard it's good.
Maybe I should try it.
Terraria on DRank?
I forgot how...
By the way, guys, so you can't look at those ranks and compare it to other rankings online.
So the way it works is that the tiers on that website right now are made from the library that is there.
And the library that I have on the website is already an excellent library.
So the way you have to think about it is that a D tier game, or a C tier, is a C tier game in a library of already excellent games.
It's like if I asked you your three top games and then put one of them on S, the other one on A, and the other one on B.
You have to put them somewhere, right?
Yeah.
And having a score of 50 does not mean it's bad.
That literally means it is the middle of the pack of an awesome library.
You know?
Because I really hate this frickin' culture nowadays where a game that gets a score of 6 is considered terrible.
Frickin' use the whole scale!
1 to 100!
What's the point?
You know?
It's so dumb.
And people are up in arms about games getting a rating of 7, which is like, pretty good!
7 out of 10!
That's a good rating!
We should use the whole scale.
Yeah, I mean, you almost never see a game that is 2 out of 10.
Why not?
Ratings are pointless most of the time.
Yeah, I guess they are.
But they are an indication of, you know, the zeitgeist.
In some way.
You can use it to get a rough idea of the quality of a game, and then, obviously, you gotta try it yourself and play it, and...
It can go either way, obviously.
But chances are, you're gonna...
There's a higher chance you're gonna like a game that is very well-received than not, right?
Like, even my favorite game of all time, World of Warcraft, on that scale is a 93.
And for it to go to 100, it would be like...
It is almost mathematically impossible.
It would have to be a preference...
Odds of like a million to one.
At that point, which is just unrealistic.
The scale on the website right now cannot even distinguish between 5,000 to one and like a thousand to one.
Because even at that point, you know, it doesn't even make sense.
Just talk about odds at that scale.
It's crazy.
Wait, is it actually a 3.3 on the side?
That would be too funny.
I didn't actually make it that way.
Expedit, let me see.
Oh, no, it's not.
It said 16 plus minus eight.
That's another thing.
The uncertainties there are real uncertainties.
It's actually two sigma.
So 95%.
So pretty much you can assume that if a game has an uncertainty and another game has another uncertainty and they overlap, you can see them as ties.
That's how you should read these things.
It's two sigma.
Yeah, it's two sigma for me.
Two standard errors.
Will you start Cuphead anytime soon?
Probably not.
I've seen some gameplay from that game.
It doesn't really look like my cup of tea.
I gotta be honest.
But I...
Maybe one day.
Perhaps.
I heard it's very difficult.
Pun intended?
Wait, what?
What pun?
Did I somehow do something clever just now?
Oh, Cuphead!
No, that was not a pun.
That was not intended.
That was completely unintended.
That's so funny, actually.
I wonder if because I said cup...
Uh...
Why did I say...
I wanted to say Copland, but that's a movie with Sylvester Stallone.
Cuphead!
I wonder if that planted a seed in my subconscious about cups and then I said cup of tea.
Probably, right?
You're welcome, Noecky.
I'm glad you're liking the videos.
I do plan on playing Deltarune when it's finished.
I'm gonna let the guy cook first, you know?
I'm not gonna start eating his soup when it's half raw.
Ooh!
Is the to beat thing the average time or how long it took you?
No, to beat is sourced publicly from IGDB.
The playtime is my time that I spent on the game and it's sourced from my YouTube playlists.
It's calculated from there.
The to beat is like the average time to beat without going and collecting all the collectibles and doing all the stuff.
You know, there's like multiple tiers of that.
It's just for comparison's sake.
It's fun statistics, I guess.
I'm eating the soup as soon as the ingredients are grown from the ground up.
Okay.
You do you, man.
Any reason you have only Psychonauts 2 but not 1?
No.
Not at all.
Honestly, I probably should put Psychonauts 1 and remove Psychonauts 2.
Because it's gonna inflate the library.
You know, I actually did go through and remove some sequels and stuff.
Just because it's too much.
So I should definitely exchange that one.
I also noticed that for Pikmin 2...
I think it's because someone may have mentioned in chat, saying, You gotta play Pikmin 2.
And then I was like, okay, I'll add it to the list, you know?
Yeah, I'll have to do a pass and remove some of those.
By the way guys, I'm making something right now, where you guys can go in and vote.
So the way this works, and I think it's gonna be really fun.
The way I have it set up now, it's just in alpha, I guess.
I don't really... it's not really ready.
But basically, you're gonna get a selection of all the 122 games that I played, And then you deselect all the ones you never played.
Right?
And then you click next.
And then it's gonna give you 30 to 40 comparisons between the games that are left, the ones you have played.
And it's gonna save it into a database.
And then everyone else does this, and it all gets compiled into one...
Into one preference.
And we're gonna compare that to my preference.
And see how much it diverges.
And the cool thing about it is, I'm probably gonna put in a timer.
So that you only have like 3 or 4 seconds to choose, so it's truly gut instinct.
You know?
You can't think too much about it.
You gotta be super honest about which game you prefer in the moment.
I think it could be really fun to see.
Will every person's rating have the same weight, or will people that vote more have more impact?
Well, the way I'm gonna do it is, I'm only gonna give people 30 to 50 comparisons, and then no more.
I guess some people are gonna find ways to circumvent that by, I don't know, deleting cache, or VPNing, or whatever.
I can't really get rid of that.
But no, it's gonna count equally as much, I guess.
But I'm gonna have systems in place that will detect whether or not a person is just clicking, like, really quickly, not really choosing, you know?
It's easy to see that in the data.
You can clean that up pretty easily.
But it should count the same.
What's my Gander?
I don't know.
I have heard of Mechanarium!
Is that the one RTS game?
Because then I really wanted to play it.
Oh no wait, this is something else.
No, I have not played that one.
I think it's in my backlog, though.
Rating the general game series would save a lot of space.
Half-Life 1, 2, Alyx...
Ah...
Yeah, but the thing is though, like, there's so many games, at least in my library, where...
The fourth game is, like, terrible.
And the third game is amazing, and the second is a masterpiece, and the first is legendary.
You know?
So I really do consider them separate games.
Have you ever tried Hollow Knight?
Yeah, yeah, I've played it!
I've played Hollow Knight and Silksong.
They're both on my YouTube.
Amazing games.
Ha ha ha!
Go check it out.
I think...
Let me check if Machinarium actually is on the backlog.
Oh, it...
Wait, is it Machinarium?
Oh, it is.
It's Machinarium.
It is in the backlog.
Okay.
Have you ever tried Isaac?
No, no, no.
But I want to.
Yeah, I bought Silksong three times.
I paid full price for that game, guys.
60 bucks.
Although, nowadays, apparently 60 bucks isn't gonna cut it.
For the new games.
GTA 6 is gonna be 80 bucks and 100 bucks for the expanded edition or whatever.
That's crazy.
And that's probably for a...
Only console version in 30 frames per second as well.
It's like, damn, dude.
That's steep.
I've not played Uncharted, but I want to.
I've heard they're good.
Especially the later ones.
I don't know if I'd enjoy Lunaset.
I don't know what it is.
But I think it's on my list.
I recognize the name.
Yeah, it's on the list.
I hate that Sony's trying to get rid of physical game copies.
Honest, I don't even care.
I gotta be honest.
It's inevitable.
I mean, we live in a world where everything is digital nowadays.
Are you really surprised?
I'm not.
I'm surprised it's happening this late.
Interesting.
You rated Silksong higher than the Hollow Knight before the statistical thing.
Now it's the opposite.
That's the thing.
That's so interesting about this Dawn.
This one is much more truthful.
And I think it has something to do with the fact that I had just finished Silksong, you know?
So I had recency bias.
Which is a big thing.
But when you're doing this, you can't really lie to the system, you know?
So it's gonna count...
Like, it's more truthful than I can ever be.
If you tell someone or ask someone to make a...
a list of their favorite games and rank everything, you know, from a 1 to a 100, absolutely.
That is almost impossible to do.
Because you keep saying to yourself, Oh, but wait, if this guy is at 83 and the other guy was at 82, but I like the 82 more, so I gotta move that up and then it's a mess.
It's a real mess.
There's a lot of surprises in that list now, now that I did the comparisons.
Some games that I rated a lot higher, probably because of recency bias, are now much lower.
The cool thing is, though, I have timestamps for all these comparisons.
So over time, when I do more and more and more, also as new games get added, I can make, like, some kind of graph or comparison of how my taste or preferences change over time.
You know, that could be some interesting data angle there.
I store all kinds of information.
I even store response time and which ones I pick, left or right, and how often, and stuff like that, you know.
Could be kind of fun.
What if you voted right after finishing the game?
Wouldn't that still be affected by recency bias?
It would!
And that's why someone else mentioned this on the Discord, actually.
And I think what I'm gonna do is that when I finish a game, I'm not going to vote it or enter it into the voting until I have finished the next game.
So the game I'm incorporating is always one game behind.
Because recency bias is real.
And there's also, you know, rose-tinted glasses about older games, and I'm definitely guilty of that.
You know, when I did the comparisons, I was looking at Spyro, you know?
Like, that's one of the comparisons.
I'm like, damn, I had so much fun with that as a kid.
But if I played it now, I don't know if I would like it as much.
I'm basing that off my memory of how much I liked it, right?
Yeah, Ducky Bird, exactly.
Isaac is not getting rated anytime soon.
I mean, Isaac is...
It's a good game, man.
I was about to give it a rating, but then I remembered, don't do that.
Let the system decide that for you.
How much time did you get when you were doing your comparisons?
Infinite time.
I didn't put a timer on myself.
It did record the response time, though.
Like, that data is there.
But I didn't actually put a timer on it.
I'm just playing with the idea of putting the timer there for you guys.
Maybe I won't do it.
Maybe I'll have it as, like, an option.
No, no, because it needs to be the same for everyone.
Yeah, I don't know yet.
How much would you guys hate if you had to make an account to do the voting on the website?
Because that is one way to do, like, a capture and make sure there's no bots or something like that.
Because...
I would probably be a little annoyed having to make an account.
So I totally get that, you know?
It would be better in the long run, but it's also, like, a friction to get people to vote.
It's much easier to just give a link and they can instantly start voting, right?
Not to be that guy, but I would love for you to give Terraria another chance.
Maybe if there's, like, an update 4.0, I'll check it out.
But honestly, I just don't really like that game very much.
And contrary to popular belief, it had nothing to do with the difficulty that I chose.
I have many qualms with that game.
I love making accounts.
Nobody loves making accounts.
Like, one of the worst things ever.
I could auth with Twitch.
But it's still...
The whole idea of making an account.
Yeah, we'll see.
I, uh...
Maybe I'll store all your data, you know?
Maybe I'll store your device and your operating system, your browser, everything, so I can fingerprint you and make sure you can't cheat.
I think that's actually against some EU laws.
So I technically can't do that, I think.
I'm not gonna do that.
But I'll definitely make some kind of, uh...
Cloudflare thing, I think.
Some invisible Cloudflare turnstile...
Something.
Because that's an easy win.
Have to give a blood sample to a vote.
I like that!
Or you have to mail in your votes to a physical address.
What do you think of that?
Alright, I'm out of here.
Thanks for watching, guys.
This was great.
Another unbeaten run.
At least in terms of the streaks.
I'll see you in the next stream slash video.
Bye-bye.